{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: lion", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["later", "to", "and", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: hunters", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["him", "and", "hunters", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["of", "him", "lion", "by"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: take", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "take", "zoo", "After"]}, {"explanation": "idea is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the _____________ of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["mouse", "tree", "wagon", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["to", "later", "few", "a"]}, {"explanation": "he is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"he\", Personal pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the _____________ , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["mouse", "tree", "lion", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "help is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to _____________ him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["take", "go", "let", "help"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: and", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "and", "a", "the"]}, {"explanation": "went is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they _____________ in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lifted", "was", "tied", "went"]}, {"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["that", "by", "of", "After"]}, {"explanation": "the is Determiner", "question": "Is \"the\", Verb (past participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: of", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lion", "was", "paw", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "that", "search", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "a", "him", "went"]}, {"explanation": "to is to", "question": "Is \"to\", Foreign word in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "was is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion _____________ so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["tied", "went", "was", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "captured is Verb (past participle)", "question": "Is \"captured\", Verb (past participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"of\", Verb (present participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "take is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to _____________ him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["take", "let", "help", "go"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Select appropiate Adverb from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["sometime", "later", "Sometime", "so"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"tree\", Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"of\", Possessive WH-pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: by", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["help", "was", "by", "the"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"that\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"search\", WH-determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "and is Coordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"and\", Coordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "able is Adjective", "question": "Is \"able\", Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: wagon", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "wagon", "went", "the"]}, {"explanation": "the is Determiner", "question": "Is \"the\", Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled _____________ the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["by", "that", "in", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["lifted", "him", "was", "paw"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: The", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["paw", "by", "and", "The"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Is \"Sometime\", Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After _____________ they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["in", "that", "after", "of"]}], "success": 1}